pcrush.com 2018-01-06

# Privacy Policy | pcRUSH.com

As our customer, your privacy is important to us. We will never sell or share your personally identifiable information without your prior consent, except that which is necessary as described below. We gather certain types of information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, promotions and contests. Third party companies may be used to facilitate fulfillment, shipping, marketing, customer service, payment processing, and other functions necessary to provide the most rewarding experience to our customers. Information shared with these companies is handled securely and with the highest degree of care. 

Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we gather and how we use them.

## Information That We Collect

pcRUSH.com collects two types of information from customers which are stored in a secure database: voluntary information (such as name, e-mail address, billing and shipping addresses, phone, and credit card information) and automatic information (such as number of visits and browser used).

## Voluntary Information

Voluntary information is personally identifiable information that our customers provide when registering with pcRUSH.com. It makes it possible for them to purchase items, receive electronic newsletters and enter contests and other promotional opportunities provided by pcRUSH.com. We also maintain a record of customer product interests and purchase history from our site in order to better supply products. This information is also necessary for us to process and ship orders, inquire our customers about purchases, and inform them about occasional special offers.

## Automatic Information

Automatic information is non-personally identifiable information that we receive and store whenever you interact with us. As with many other Web sites, we use "cookies" which are small data files stored on your computer. The information we receive when your Web browser accesses pcRUSH.com includes the following: 

  * IP address - to measure our site traffic, diagnose problems with our server and administer over our Web site.
  * Referral site - if you come to our site via a link from another Web site, the location of the referral is noted. This is used to help us know where some of our users come from.
  * Browser type - to help us optimize our site to match the latest technology used by our customers.
  * Number of visits - so we can offer special promotions to regular customers and provide a more personalized shopping experience.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off on your browser. If you turn off cookies, you will not be able to make a purchase from our site. However, you will still be able to browse our site without any problem.

## California Residents

If you are a California resident and have a established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to:

Atman, Inc dba pcRUSH.com  
Attn: California Privacy Rights  
1325 E. El Segundo Blvd.  
El Segundo, CA 90245  
United States 

Please allow 30 days for a response.

If you are a California resident under 18 years old and a registered user, you can request that we remove content or information that you have posted to our website or other online services. Note that fulfillment of the request may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal (e.g., if the content or information has been reposted by another user). To request removal of content or information, please email [california-privacy@pcrush.com](mailto:california-privacy@pcrush.com "Send Email to california-privacy@pcrush.com") or call 1-888-205-7777.
